Unrest in Peace
The Gravedancers is a horror, thriller film directed by Mike Mendez.
After a night of drunken exploits, Allison, Harris, and Kira are chased and
terrorized by the ghosts of a child pyromaniac, an ax murderer, and a rapist.
Harris McKay, played by Dominic Purcell.
Kira Hayden, played by Josie Maran.
Allison Mitchell, played by Clare Kramer.
Sid Vance, played by Marcus Thomas.
Vincent Cochet, played by Tchéky Karyo.
Frances Culpepper, played by Megahn Perry.
The Gravedancers is a 2006 American horror film directed by Mike Mendez.
It was chosen as one of the 8 Films To Die For in 2006 and screened
at that year's After Dark Horrorfest film festival.
The film explores themes of envelope, childhood friends, ghost, graveyard.
The tone is dark and intense.